Guide to the J.G. Link and Company Records 1939-1965
Montana State University-Bozeman Library
- Project Files, 1939-1965; Series 4
  - Headquarters Fire Station – Frank L. Pirtz (Box-folder 10/18)
  - Headquarters Fire Station – Midland Electric (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Headquarters Fire Station – Star Service (Box-folder 10/20)
  - First National Bank, Powell, Wyoming – General File, September 1, 1979 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Floral Park Service Station Addition – Butte, Montana, 1961 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Fraser Playground (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Fraser, Willard – Indian Affairs Building (Box-folder 10/24)
  - Fraser, Willard E. – Nursing Home (Box-folder 10/25)
  - Fred R. Griffey – Garage (Box-folder 10/26)
    [1344; 090]
  - Gallatin Gateway Trailer Camp (Box-folder 10/27)
  - Gallatin Gateway – 25 Trailers (Box-folder 10/28)
  - Garfield County Hospital – Jordan Montana, 1964 (Box-folder 10/29)
  - Garfield County Hospital (Box-folder 10/30)
  - Garfield County Hospital – Jordan, Montana – All Correspondence, 1944–1953 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - Garfield County Jail – All Correspondence and Contracts – Jordan Montana, 1948–1954 (Box-folder 11/1)
    [2220; 207]
  - Garfield County Hospital – Jordan, MT – Contracts, Bids, Estimates, etc. (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Geise, Tony (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Glasgow Nursing Home – Valley City (Box-folder 11/4)
    [2220; 182]
  - Glasgow Montana – Comprehensive Master Plan (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Glendive – Sacred Heart Parochial School (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Gordon Residence – General (Box-folder 11/7)
    [2220; 375]
  - Gottsche Center – Thermopolis (Box-folder 11/8)
  - Government Building – Agriculture Department – Sidney Research Building (Box-folder 11/9)
  - Grand Hotel (Box-folder 11/10)
    [2040; 088]
  - Grand Hotel Additions – Correspondence, 1950–1951 (Box-folder 11/11)
    [1344; 196]
  - Grand Hotel – Contracts, Estimates, etc. (Box-folder 11/12)
  - Great Northern Tool and Supply Company – Billings, Montana (Box-folder 11/13)
    [1344; 147]
  - Harlowton Swimming Pool (Box-folder 11/14)
    [1344; 025]
  - Harlowton Pool: Collection (Box-folder 11/15)
  - Harlowton Moose Heating, 1952 (Box-folder 11/16)
    [1344; 112]
  - Hawthorne School: Collection (Box-folder 11/17)
    [1344; 134]
  - Havre Border Patrol – Change Orders and Proposals and Records of Change Orders (Box-folder 11/18)
    [2220; 200]
  - Havre Border Patrol Sector HDQ – Contracts and Contract Payments (Box-folder 11/19)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Contracts (Box-folder 11/20)
  - Havre Border Patrol Sector HQ – Correspondence, 1963–1965 (Box-folder 11/21)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Correspondence – Morgen and Oswood (Box-folder 11/22)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Inspection File Correspondence – Morgen and Oswood (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Correspondence – Miscellaneous (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Havre Border Patrol - - Inspection File – Correspondence – G.S.A. (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Daily Diaries – Regan and Link (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Correspondence – G.S.A. (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Inspection Report (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Inspection Report – Form 2230 by Principal of Firm (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Inspection Report – by Mechanical Engineer (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Electrical Systems Outlines (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Inspection Reports (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Photos (Box-folder 12/12)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Inspection File – Progress Report Schedule and Payments (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Progress Reports Schedule and Payments (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Progress Reports (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Records of Proposals and Contract Changes (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Havre Border Patrol Sector HDQ – Submittals, 1963–1964 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Supervision Hours – Correspondence – Contracts and Payments (Box-folder 12/18)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Railing Details: Collection (Box-folder 12/19)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Sector HQ’s – Forms and Masters (Box-folder 12/20)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Transmittal Letters – 51 – 100 (Box-folder 12/21)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Transmittal Letters – 1 – 25 (Box-folder 12/22)
  - Havre Border Patrol Sector HQ’s (Box-folder 12/23)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Inspection Reports – Work Under Contract (Box-folder 12/24)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Tests: Compaction, Concrete, etc., 1965 (Box-folder 12/25)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Transmittal Letters – 26 – 50 (Box-folder 12/26)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Inspector File – Transmittal Letter – 10 25 (Box-folder 12/27)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Transmittal Letters – 51 – 75 (Box-folder 12/28)
  - Havre Border Patrol – Transmittal Letters – 26 – 50 (Box-folder 12/29)
  - Hart – Albin Company File (Box-folder 12/30)
    [863; 114]
  - Hesse, Geo, Res, Remodel – 301 – Clarke (Box-folder 12/31)
    [1344; 087]
  - Holy Name Convent, 1960 (Box-folder 12/32)
  - Holy Name Convent Estimates – Contacts, 1961 (Box-folder 12/33)
  - Holy Name Rectory and Miscellaneous – Reverend Kimmett – Sheridan Wyoming, 1954–1959 (Box-folder 12/34)
  - Holy Rosary – Billings, Montana (Box-folder 12/35)
  - Holy Rosary – Lander, Wyoming – Fr. Scullion, 1963 (Box-folder 12/36)
  - Holy Name Convent – Miscellaneous Drawings (Box-folder 13/1)
  - Holy Rosary – Miles City (Box-folder 13/2)
  - Hoven, Gordon (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Hysham Gym, 1938 (Box-folder 13/4)
    [863; 064]
  - Immaculate Conception School and Gym – Construction, Contracts, Estimates, etc. (Box-folder 13/5)
  - Immaculate Conception School – Forsyth, Montana, 1953–1960 (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Indian Agencies – Promotion and General Correspondence (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Industrial Equipment Company (Box-folder 13/8)
    [1344; 102]
  - Ingomar – Office Set (Box-folder 13/9)
  - Johnston Building – Beach, North Dakota (Box-folder 13/10)
  - Jordan (Box-folder 13/11)
  - Jordan Swimming Pools – Working Drawings (Box-folder 13/12)
    [2220; 206]
  - Leachman Residence (Box-folder 13/13)
  - Jordan Swimming Pool – Correspondence (Box-folder 13/14)
  - Joseph Lyden – Butte, Montana – Crown Cigar Store (Box-folder 13/15)
    [1344; 095]
  - Kalaris Building (Box-folder 13/16)
  - Kenco Pump House – General (Box-folder 13/17)
  - Koko, 1959–1963 (Box-folder 13/18)
    [1344; 122]
  - Koko Club – Specifications (Box-folder 13/19)
  - Klamm Properties – Miles City, Montana – General (Box-folder 13/20)
    [2220; 355]
  - Kraft – Raleigh – Res. (Box-folder 13/21)
  - KRJF Broadcasting Station Miles City, Montana (Box-folder 13/22)
  - Lambert Gym, 1940–1946 (Box-folder 13/23)
    [863; 059]
  - Laurel School Gym (Box-folder 13/24)
    [1344; 045]
  - Lewis and Clark County Hospital, 1937–1938 (Box-folder 13/25)
  - Lewiston Mental Health Center (Box-folder 13/26)
  - Lockwood Junior High – Mechanical – Job #5210 (Box-folder 13/27)
  - Lockwood School – Billings, Montana (Box-folder 13/28)
  - Malta – Grade School (Box-folder 13/29)
  - Malta Swimming Pool, 1953–1954 (Box-folder 13/30)
    [2220; 232]
  - Manhattan School Addition, 1960–1961 (Box-folder 13/31)
  - Marillac Hall Remodeling Feasibility Study (Box-folder 13/32)
  - Math-Physics Building, 1962 (Box-folder 13/33)
  - Math-Physics Laboratory Building – Montana State College – Bozeman, Montana – Correspondence, 1951–1954 (Box-folder 13/34)
  - Mazanec – Correspondence with Dickinson Office – Interoffice (Box-folder 13/35)
  - McClurg, A.C. Building (Box-folder 13/36)
  - MC Cone County Court House – Correspondence (Box-folder 13/37)
  - MC Cone County Courthouse – General Contractor Circle – John Sterhan (Box-folder 13/38)
  - MC Cone County Courthouse – Plumbing and Heating – Circle – S.J. Daniel and Sons (Box-folder 13/39)
  - MC Cone County Courthouse – Progress Reports (Box-folder 13/40)
  - MC Cone County Courthouse – Computations (Box-folder 14/1)
  - MC Cone County Hospital – Circle, Montana – Correspondence (Box-folder 14/2)
  - McGladery Hendrickson (Box-folder 14/3)
  - McMullen – Computer Area (Box-folder 14/4)
    [2220; 004, 060, and 077]
  - McMullen Hall – Computer Room – Payment File (Box-folder 14/5)
  - McMullen Hall – Contract Supervisor – Change Orders (Box-folder 14/6)
  - McMullen Hall – Correspondence (Box-folder 14/7)
  - McMullen – Entrance Steps – Correspondence (Box-folder 14/8)
  - McMullen – Entrance Steps – Payment File (Box-folder 14/9)
  - McMullen Hall – Existing Drawings – Payment File (Box-folder 14/10)
  - McMullen Hall – List of Approvals: Collection (Box-folder 14/11)
  - McMullen Hall Remodel – Midland Electric (Box-folder 14/12)
  - McMullen Hall Remodel – Phil R. Morrow (Box-folder 14/13)
  - McMullen Hall Remodel – Spildie Construction Company (Box-folder 14/14)
  - McMullen Hall – Third Floor Corridor Renovations – Correspondence (Box-folder 14/15)
  - McMullen – Third Floor Corridor Renovations – Contracts and Payment File (Box-folder 14/16)
  - McMullen – Third Floor Corridor Renovations – Working Drawings (Box-folder 14/17)
  - McMullen Hall – Plan Holders (Box-folder 14/18)
  - McMullen Hall – Working Drawings (Box-folder 14/19)
  - McNamer Residence (Box-folder 14/20)
  - Meagher County (Box-folder 14/21)
  - Medicine Lake School Additions – Correspondence, 1953–1955 (Box-folder 14/22)
  - Medicine Lake School Additions – Contracts, Progress Reports, Computations (Box-folder 14/23)
  - Melcher Residence (Box-folder 14/24)
    [2220; 175]
  - Melstone School – Travis Jam, 1967 (Box-folder 14/25)
    [2220; 236]
  - Metra – Correspondence (Box-folder 14/26)
  - Midland Empire Fair, 1946–1950 (Box-folder 15/1)
    [863; 160]
  - Midland National Bank’s Kiosk (Box-folder 15/2)
  - Miles City Civic Center, 1958 (Box-folder 15/3)
  - Minot, North Dakota Job – (Sacred Heart Convent and Academy) – Mother Amita (Box-folder 15/4)
  - Montana Power Company (Box-folder 15/5)
    [863; 113]
  - Montana State College Green House – Miscellaneous (Box-folder 15/6)
  - Montana State College Green House, 1957–1959 (Box-folder 15/7)
  - Montana State College Green House – Drawings (Box-folder 15/8)
  - Montana State Industrial School – Adjust. Cott. – Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box-folder 15/9)
    [2220; 240, 240b, 248, and 248b]
  - Montana State Industrial School – Adjust. Cott. – Willis Construction Company – Contractor (Box-folder 15/10)
  - Montana State Industrial School – Administration Building – Correspondence, 1953–1954 (Box-folder 15/11)
  - Montana State Industrial School – All Work (Box-folder 15/12)
  - Montana State Industrial School, Cottage and Kitchen (Box-folder 15/13)
  - Montana State Industrial School – Boys Cottage – Correspondence, 1951–1954 (Box-folder 15/14)
  - Montana State Industrial School – Boys Cottage – Holzworth Construction Company, Miles City, May 21, 1952 (Box-folder 15/15)
  - Montana State Industrial School – Boys Cottage Kitchen Alterations – Progress Reports (Box-folder 15/16)
  - Montana State Industrial School – C and H Construction Company, 1953–1954 (Box-folder 15/17)
  - Montana State Industrial School – J.F. Regan and Sons, 1953–1954 (Box-folder 15/18)
  - Montana State Industrial School – Miles City (Box-folder 15/19)
  - Montana State Industrial School – Statements Issued, 1967 (Box-folder 15/20)
  - Montana State – U.C.C. Building – Billings, 1957 (Box-folder 15/21)
  - Montana State – U.C.C. Building – Butte Montana, 1957–1959 (Box-folder 15/22)
  - Montana State – Unemployment Compensation Building – All Work, 1957–1959 (Box-folder 15/23)
  - Montana State – U.C.C. Building – Glendive Montana, 1958–1960 (Box-folder 15/24)
  - Montana State – U.C.C. Building – Miles City, Montana, 1957–1959 (Box-folder 15/25)
  - Montana State University Remodeling – Contracts and Statement File (Box-folder 15/26)
  - Montana State University Remodeling – General (Box-folder 15/27)
  - Montana State University Remodeling – Inspection Reports (Box-folder 15/28)
  - Montana State University Remodeling – J.R. Baker Construction Company (Box-folder 16/1)
  - Montana State University Remodeling – Service Electric (Box-folder 16/2)
  - Montana State University Remodeling – Shop Drawings (Box-folder 16/3)
  - Montana State University Remodeling – Working Drawings (Box-folder 16/4)
  - Montana – Veterinary Research, 1963–1964 (Box-folder 16/5)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Laboratory – Incinerators – Literature – American Incinerator Company (Box-folder 16/6)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Laboratory – Incinerators (Temperature Controls) – Burling Temperature Controls (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Laboratory – Bozeman Electric – Elec. Contr. (Box-folder 16/8)
  - Montana Veterinary Research and Livestock Sanitary Board Diagnostic Lab. – Correspondence, 1958; 1959 (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Isolation Building – Correspondence and Inspection Reports (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Montana Veterinary Research and Livestock Sanitary Board Diagnostic Laboratory – Correspondence, 1960 (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Laboratory Incinerators – Drawings Literature etc. – Goder (Box-folder 16/12)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Laboratory Incinerators – Literature and Drawings etc. – Denver Fire Clay (Box-folder 16/13)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Laboratory – Incinerators – Literature, etc. – The Economy Company (Box-folder 16/14)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Laboratory – Incinerators – Burner – Eclipse Fuel Engr. C. (Box-folder 16/15)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Isolation Laboratory – Edsall Construction, 1966 (Box-folder 16/16)
  - Montana State – Veterinary Research Laboratory – General Correspondence, March 1, 1960–June 17, 1963 (Box-folder 16/17)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Laboratory Healy PBG and Heating – Mech. Contr. (Box-folder 16/18)
  - Montana State – Veterinary Research Lab. – Haggerty – Messmer Construction Company (Box-folder 16/19)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Laboratory – Incinerators – Literature and Correspondence (Box-folder 16/20)
  - Montana State – Veterinary Research – Laboratory, 1965 (Box-folder 16/21)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Laboratory – Incinerators – Morse Boulger (Box-folder 16/22)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Laboratory – Incinerators – Heimbach – Incinomite Incinerator Products – O’Hara (Box-folder 16/23)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Laboratory – Incinerators – Literature etc. – Pilbrico and Richter Inc. Companies (Box-folder 16/24)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Isolation Building – Safeway Plumbing, 1966 (Box-folder 17/1)
  - Montana State Research Laboratory – Incinerator Literature – Sargent (Box-folder 17/2)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Laboratory – Specifications (Box-folder 17/3)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Laboratory – Specifications #2 (Box-folder 17/4)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Isolation Building – Statements Issued (Box-folder 17/5)
  - Montana State Veterinary Research Isolation Building – Yellowstone Elec., 1966 (Box-folder 17/6)
  - Moose Lodge, Glendive (Box-folder 17/7)
    [863; 069]
  - Moose Lodge, Harlowton – Job No. 5204 (Box-folder 17/8)
  - Morrison C. Lewis (Box-folder 17/9)
  - Mortuary – Michelotti – Sawyers (Box-folder 17/10)
  - Motor Transit Company – Ellis and Clara House, Billings, 1948 (Box-folder 17/11)
  - Mrs. Jessie L. Hampton – Worland, Wyoming – 2 Story Store and Office (Box-folder 17/12)
  - Montana State Welfare – Federal Bldg. Vending Stand (Box-folder 17/13)
  - Multi – Use, Building – Architects Field Report (Box-folder 17/14)
  - Multi – Use Building – Concrete Tests and Other Tests by Northern Testing Lab (Box-folder 17/15)
  - Multi - Use Building – Requests For Payment (Box-folder 17/16)
  - Multi – Use Building – Correspondence, December 1969 thru excavation (Box-folder 17/17)
  - Multi – Use Building – General Correspondence – Construction (Box-folder 17/18)
  - Multi – Use Building – General Correspondence, January 1, 1975 through December 31, 1975 (Box-folder 17/19)
  - Multi – Use Building – Kober Construction (Box-folder 17/20)
  - Multi – Use Building – Kober Construction, January 1, 1975 (Box-folder 17/21)
  - Multi – Use – Miscellaneous Masters (Box-folder 17/22)
  - Multi – Use Building – Payment File (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Multi – Use Building – Schematics and Specifications (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Multi – Use Building – Specifications (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Multi – Use Building – Structural Modifications (Box-folder 18/4)
  - Multi – Use Building – Wagner Plumbing (Box-folder 18/5)
  - Multi – Use Building – Yellowstone Electric (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Mystic Lake Addition, 1957–1953 (Box-folder 18/7)
    [2220; 346]
  - Nelson – Whittinghill (Box-folder 18/8)
    [1344; 075]
  - Northwest Improvement Company – Colstrip, Montana (Box-folder 18/9)
  - Northwestern National Life Insurance (Box-folder 18/10)
  - Office Building – Gierke (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Our Lady Guadalupe Church – Pueblo, Colorado – Bishop Williging (Box-folder 18/12)
    [1344; 190]
  - Penwell Residence – Billings, 1953–1954 (Box-folder 18/13)
    [1344; 061]
  - Phillipsburg Swimming Pool Building (Box-folder 18/14)
  - Photography (Box-folder 18/15)
  - Plan Holder Records, 1948–1956 (Box-folder 18/16)
  - Plentywood (Box-folder 18/17)
    [863; 303]
  - Plentywood Elementary School – Contracts, Estimates, etc. – Arved Carlson (Box-folder 18/18)
  - Plentywood School – Elmer Johnson Plumbing and Heating (Box-folder 18/19)
  - Plentywood Elementary School – Progress Reports (Box-folder 18/20)
  - Plentywood Elementary School – Contracts, Estimates, etc. Gate City Elec. (Box-folder 18/21)
  - Plentywood Elementary School – Correspondence, 1949 (Box-folder 18/22)
  - Plains Pool – General: Collection (Box-folder 18/23)
    [2220; 254]
  - Prairie County Court House (Box-folder 18/24)
  - Pryor Community Building (Box-folder 18/25)
  - Red Lodge Schools – Red lodge, Montana, 1949 (Box-folder 18/26)
    [863; 056]
  - Reine East – Shop Drawings (Box-folder 18/27)
  - Renner – Father Mark – Strasburg – North Dakota – Gym (Box-folder 18/28)
  - Reverend H.H. Heidker, Great Falls (Box-folder 18/29)
  - Rialto Theater – Terry, Montana – Harry Burt Lee (Box-folder 18/30)
  - Rocky Mountain Gas Company – Powell Wyoming (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Rocky Boy Housing – Project Manuals (Box-folder 19/2)
    [2220; 282]
  - Rosebud High School – Correspondence, 1953–1954 (Box-folder 19/3)
    [2220; 176]
  - Roundup Court House, 1939–1940 (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Roundup Elderly Housing – General (Box-folder 19/5)
  - Roundup Memorial Hospital (Box-folder 19/6)
  - Sacred Heart – Glendive (Box-folder 19/7)
    [1344; 194]
  - Sacred Heart – Glendive #2 (Box-folder 19/8)
  - Sacred Heart School – Miles City, Montana (Box-folder 19/9)
  - Safeway Stores – Helena, Anaconda, Butte, Powell, Sidney, Glendive, Billings, Great Falls, 1939–1942 (Box-folder 19/10)
    [863; 022, 046, 047, 049, 105, 106, 108, 203]
  - Safeway Stores – Inc. (Box-folder 19/11)
  - Senior Citizens Community Center – General (Box-folder 19/12)
  - Shaw – Bozeman – State College (Box-folder 19/13)
  - Shaw – Miles City School and Auditorium (Box-folder 19/14)
  - Sheehy Residence – (Tom) (Box-folder 19/15)
    [1344; 167]
  - Shepherd High School – Shepherd Montanan, 1954 (Box-folder 19/16)
    [1344; 107]
  - Sheridan County Courthouse – Working Drawings (Box-folder 19/17)
    [2220; 334]
  - Sheridan Elks Lodge (Box-folder 19/18)
    [1344; 013]
  - Sheridan Law Enforcement Center – Electrical (Box-folder 19/19)
    [2220; 332, 335]
  - Sheridan Law Enforcement Center – General (Box-folder 19/20)
  - Sheridan Law Enforcement Center – Mechanical (Box-folder 19/21)
  - Sheridan Law Enforcement Center – Supplementary Drawings (Box-folder 19/22)
  - Slovarp – Crow Reservation (Box-folder 19/23)
  - Stanford Pool – General (Box-folder 19/24)
  - Stillwater Law Enforcement – Shop Drawings (Box-folder 19/25)
  - St. Ann’s School – Butte, Montana – Father Plumber (Box-folder 20/1)
  - St. Anthony’s Parish – Laurel, Montana – Specifications (Box-folder 20/2)
    [2220; 209]
  - St. Anthony’s Rectory, Laurel, Montana (Box-folder 20/3)
  - St. Boniface Parish, Grenora, North Dakota (Box-folder 20/4)
    [1344; 043]
  - St. Elizabeth’s Parish (Box-folder 20/5)
    [1344; 049]
  - St. Elizabeth’s Parish #2 (Box-folder 20/6)
  - St. John’s Parish, Beach, North Dakota, 1958 (Box-folder 20/7)
    [1344; 055]
  - St. Joseph’s Hospital – Lewiston, Montana, 1945–1946 (Box-folder 20/8)
  - St. Joseph’s Hospital – Lewiston – Correspondence, 1931 (Box-folder 20/9)
  - St. Jude’s Catholic School, Havre, Montana: Collection (Box-folder 20/10)
    [2219; 067]
  - St. Mary’s H.S. Addition – Richardton, North Dakota (Box-folder 20/11)
  - St. Michael’s Church – Absarokee – Father Kelly (Box-folder 20/12)
  - St. Michaels’s Church – Absarokee – Specifications (Box-folder 20/13)
  - St. Patrick’s School, Butte, Montana (Box-folder 20/14)
  - St. Phiulomena Parish School – Sidney (Box-folder 20/15)
  - St. Pius Parochial School and Church and Convent – Billings Montana (Box-folder 20/16)
    [1344; 006]
  - St. Thomas – Office Set (Box-folder 20/17)
    [2220; 006, 057]
  - St. Wenceslaus Convent and Rectory – Dickinson, North Dakota – All Correspondence (Box-folder 20/18)
    [863; 199]
  - St. Wenceslaus – Dickinson (Box-folder 20/19)
  - Sukin Brothers – Remodeling – King Clothing (Box-folder 20/20)
    [2220; 387]
  - Superior High School – Superior, Montana – Also Swimming Pool (Box-folder 20/21)
    [2220; 303]
  - Sweet Grass Community Clinic – Big Timber, Montana – All Correspondence (Box-folder 20/22)
  - Terry School (Box-folder 21/1)
    [863; 134]
  - Thornquist Residence (Box-folder 21/2)
  - T.P.S. Holy Rosary (Box-folder 21/3)
  - Trinity High School – B and K Electric (Box-folder 21/4)
  - Trinity High School Convent (Box-folder 21/5)
  - Trinity High school – Dickinson, North Dakota – Correspondence – General (Box-folder 21/6)
  - Trinity High School – Dickinson, North Dakota, 1960 (Box-folder 21/7)
  - Trinity High School – Specifications (Box-folder 21/8)
  - Trinity High School – General Correspondence, 1963–1964 (Box-folder 21/9)
  - Trinity High School – Inspection Report (Box-folder 21/10)
  - Trinity High School – John Larson Company (Box-folder 21/11)
  - Trinity High School – Klein P and H (Box-folder 21/12)
  - Change Orders – Crow Reservation Builders (Box-folder 21/13)
    [2220; 158, 168]
  - Turnkey Mutual Help – General Correspondence (Box-folder 22/1)
  - Turnkey Mutual Help Packet (Box-folder 22/2)
  - Turnkey Mutual Help – Turnkey Handbook – (Hud Handbook) (Box-folder 22/3)
  - Turnkey Mutual Help – Unsuitable Contracts (Box-folder 22/4)
  - Turnkey Mutual Help – 13 – 14 Maps – Arial Photos (Box-folder 22/5)
  - Two Valleys – Behner Building – Mechanical (Box-folder 22/6)
    [1344; 177]
  - Valley County Courthouse – Correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 22/7)
    [2220; 180, 183]
  - Valley County Courthouse – Contracts – Supervision – Change Orders (Box-folder 22/8)
  - Valley County Courthouse – General Correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 22/9)
  - Valley City – Glasgow Courthouse (Box-folder 22/10)
  - Valley County Courthouse – Plan Holders (Box-folder 22/11)
  - Valley County Courthouse – Rainbow Electric Company, 1972 (Box-folder 22/12)
  - Valley County Courthouse – Southern Steel Company, 1972 (Box-folder 22/13)
  - Valley County Courthouse – Working Drawing Files - #1 (Box-folder 22/14)
  - Valley County Courthouse – Working Drawing Files - #2 (Box-folder 22/15)
  - Valley County Courthouse – Working Drawing Files - #3 (Box-folder 22/16)